<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Bryce Hennen]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bryce Hennen's website. I like to create fun projects that have a positive impact on the world.]]></description><link>https://bhennen.github.io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 19:40:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[How I made my free website in ;FIXME:N simple steps]]></title><description><![CDATA[In this article I will investigate the details of creating my personal website in ;FIXME:N simple steps. The tools and techniques used in…]]></description><link>https://bhennen.github.io/ultimate-website-guide/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bhennen.github.io/ultimate-website-guide/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;In this article I will investigate the details of creating my personal website in ;FIXME:N simple steps. The tools and techniques used in creating my website can be used to create any number of websites for different purposes. I wanted this website so that I could share the projects I was making and to get feedback from the community on how to improve things. There are a multitude of different projects that I want to make, so having this article will also exist as a personal up-to-date guide on how I can make these websites for my other projects. By the end of this paper someone with some technical expertise should be able to set up a free website for any use. What an awesome skill to have, that unleashes vast creative potential! Some possibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Possible websites&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eCommerce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;pros and cons&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;limitations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;alternatives&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How I Built my Free Website - A Step by Step Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Integrate with Github Pages&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;my thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am about a day in and my first impressions are: wow! This tool is very easy to use, install, set up, and understand, and update. I made a very quick build of the website that took not much time at all, and the best part is that the updates to the website occur as soon as the source code is saved. This means a good workflow would be to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have a deployed &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It feels good so far!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;would i recommend&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;!-- ## get support --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>